Second last pharmacy school term.
Hi guys, happy first day of school.
I'm going back to pharmacy school for my 3A term.
This is actually my second last pharmacy school term.
And so it's actually my second last day of school as well.
It just feels so crazy.
I just feel like my pharmacy journey has been so long.
I am taking a full course load, which is five courses and a lab, I
believe.
I usually know all my different course syllabi, like the back of my hand, but
I haven't gotten internet installed at my new apartment.
So I've been kind of slacking on the back to school prep, if I'm gonna
be honest, which is kind of stressing me out because as you guys know, like
being a student is like my number one job.
It's like the most important thing to me.
And so I really need to get to school to download everything just because my
hotspot has not been cutting it It just won't connect to my laptop for some
reason
And this is the perfect blush for me sleepy girl by road i'm so tired
it is not funny I also haven't opened my blinds completely.
So if it looks dark right now, like that's why
Last step is always powder, but I have a feeling nothing can really cover up
my four hours of sleep.
In collective, 10 hours of sleep the last two days.
Like I have not really been sleeping that much.
But we can only try our best.
I also normally wash my hair before the first day of school, but I just
didn't have time this morning because of therapy.
This is my final makeup look and now I'm going to get changed.
And now I'm all dressed.
Please ignore the boxes.
I've been living here for like three days.
This is the gas board cardigan from Cezanne.
This tank top is from Verish.
And then these jeans, I don't remember where they're from.
So I will link them on screen.
But anyways, let's head to school
I
just got out of my three-hour
lecture and i'm fading so hard you guys I feel like my attention span definitely
shortened while I was out of school for the last four months But at least
it was interesting and it's done now And now my first order of business is
to make my notion calendar with all my due dates for like assignments labs group
projects Etc because I just took a browse and it looks like a lot.
So now my friend and I are gonna go and do that
Hey
guys,
it is my second day back to school and I've just gotten ready super quickly.
I'm not doing any makeup today because I'm too tired.
Even though that probably means that I need it more because these eye bags are
no joke.
I'm wearing something really comfy again.
it's just like this plain sweater in the front but the back print is really
cool I'll put like a photo up and I'm actually up pretty early it's around
7 o'clock right now but it's because I have a lot of things to do
so yeah let's get it done
all the books that I could find from my moving boxes i've put on the
shelf i definitely have way more i just don't know where they are right now
and they're not sorted in any way whatsoever not by color not by author not
by genre it's just a mixture of things and i kind of like this look
for right
now.
And I have this Sunseeker Neota that I always put by this lamp because I
think she's so cute like that.
So this is kind of all I've got for now.
I definitely need to fill the other sections on the shelf, but decorating is supposed
to be intentional and takes some time, so I'm not going to worry about it
too much right now.
I already know it's not perfect, so yeah.
Music
I'm going
to
make a so
that's why you can't get along
Thank you.
I'm going
to
make a Thank you.
commercial Good morning guys, it is another day in the loft.
I'm a mess right now because obviously I'm still moving in and all that.
But of course, I have my desk set up and I'm just doing the patho
lecture before the therapeutics lecture, which obviously get a better understanding of the disease.
So what I'm doing is listening to the lecture and having these slides pulled up
side by side and I'm just taking out little notes and making like bottom lines
or like key takeaways for the slides that are more important and that's what i
usually do during my first pass of new content i also need to do my
grocery order so i'm going to make that list right now and then i'll either
pick it up or get it scheduled for after class
hey guys i just got in from class and i found these waiting for me
at my door i have a feeling I already know who they're from but we're
gonna read it together.
Oh my gosh It says happy housewarming brianna from garbo and ainsley and it's the
fact that i'm renting this place And I have moved seven times in the last
three years.
Obviously.
They haven't sent me flowers I haven't known them for those whole three years, but
The girls just get me And guys I actually have to show you something really
cute because they actually sent me almost the exact same thing The last time I
moved and I lived here in waterloo These girls are honestly just my best friends
in the world between the three of us It is always floral galore and i'm
just so lucky and you text them right now
Oh Like guys look how beautiful these are
Okay, and now i'm by the front door because I want to tackle some of
the packages that i've gotten recently that are Hopefully going to turn this house into
more of a home, but it's an apartment Um, number one thing is that I
want to build this armchair that I got so i'm going to start there
Thank you.
Thank
you.
um
i'll come home because i can take the train okay sorry i
just needed a little bit of a moment because i just told my parents that
i was a little bit stressed about school and i was kind of having a
bad day and their first reaction is to just come up immediately help me finish
unpacking run errands with me and bring me home quick nails but i was just
trying to tell them that I understand they're very busy and that they can't just,
you know, drive up here and they shouldn't spend so much time what some people
would call coddling or what others might just call like being caring.
But anyways, that really cheered me up and I'm going to finish putting away these
groceries.
I
got
shrimp and scallop one ton, I got another pack of frozen udon, I got sliced
beef rolls, and then I just got some bibim and peeled shrimp just for ease.
As for veggies, I just got some Chinese bok choy and some green onions, and
then also some shiitake mushrooms.
There
is
a snowstorm.
I don't know why I'm smiling.
It's going to fuck me to death.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
so
you
guys can probably already tell what i've made for dinner
but i just made some kimchi jjigae or like kimchi stew and it's only my
third or fourth time making it i think and my first home-cooked meal in this
loft.
It's obviously piping hot so I was just waiting for it to cool down but
I'm so excited for this.
It's actually really good.
Yay!
I would have been so mad if I spent an hour cooking this and it
was not good.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.